

Personal information

DOB:01/06/1991

Marital Status: Single

Religion: Islam

Visa status: visit visa

Nationality: Pakistani

Driving License: Motor Car/ Bike(PAKISTAN)

Contact

Address: Abu Dhabi (UAE)
Phone: +971-588940675

Email: numanrasheed5@gmail.com

Languages

English –Professional Urdu – Native Hindi – Working Proficiency Punjabi-Native or Bilingual

Hobbies

- Football
- National Geographic

Education

Master in Business Administration (MBA-Finance & Marketing) 2013-2016 University of central Punjab Lahore

Bachelor in commerce (2010-2012) University of the Punjab Lahore

I.com (Inter of commerce) BISE Lahore

Matriculation (Science) BISE Lahore

NUMAN UR RASHEED

Summary:

A capable and trustworthy Accountant who has extensive practical knowledge of 05 years, In fields of operational and financial activities. One who can make decisions by critical thinking.

Skill Highlights

- Leader ship and team management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solving
- Attention to Detail
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- Symbols
- SAP

Experience

Credit Officer (7 Months) March to Oct 2021



Muslim Commercial Bank (MCB) Pakistan

- Home loan
- Mortgage loan
- Evaluation of Financials
- Documentation

General Banking Officer (2 years) March 2019 to Feb 2021



Muslim Commercial Bank (MCB) Pakistan

- Inward and outward Clearing
- ATM card delivery & cheque book
- TBD handling & Foreign Remittance handling
- CDR, RTGS,DD
- MIS of Data (Weekly)
- Batch uploading

Teller Services Officer (2 years) March 2017 to Feb 2019



Muslim Commercial Bank (MCB) Pakistan

- Balancing of cash drawers
- Custodian of ATM machine
- Foreign Currency
- Prize bond

Financial Consultant Internee (3Months) June 2015 to Aug 2015



Fazal Paper Mills, Pakistan

- Prepare month end financial reports to finance manager.
 - Review Clients contracts and interpreted their financials.
 - Audited Practice data to identify inefficiencies.